Ariadna Vanegas-Rubio

(347)340-5215 | ariadna.vanegas@gmail.com | Bronx, New York linkedin.com/in/avrubio/ | github.com/avrubio

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate, technically proficient, detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me to further enhance my skills in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools JavaScript Certification | November 2022

Java Spring Data JPA o Unit Testing (JUnit, JavaScript Spring Security (JWT) Mockito) 0 HTML **SOLID OOP Principles** Bootstrap o REST API's o Dependencies Injection CSS Spring Boot o SQL Git

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | Remote | August 2022 – December 2022

Training Participant

- o Participating in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Docker

MakeInspires | Mamaroneck, New York | February 2022 – June 2022

STEM Instructor

- o Directed clear objectives for all lesson plans for Scratch programming, Minecraft architecture, Stop Motion, and projects while communicating them to students
- o Established and enforced rules for behavior and procedures for maintaining order amongst students
- Prepared and presented grade-appropriate STEM concepts presentations, while introducing students to while providing a fun, encouraging learning environment

eTeams Inc/ Lincoln Hospital | Bronx, New York | September 2021 – January 2022

Patient Care Associate (Contract)

- Communicated and collaborated with Charge Nurse and Nurse teams to provide care for patients via messaging system through an electronic health record system
- Worked with patients to quickly identify problems regarding appointments and medication and develop solutions
- o Utilized computer applications to input patient data into electronic health system

Doctor's United | White Plains, New York | November 2020 – March 2021

Medical Assistant

- o Collected and maintained accurate patient medical records
- o Utilized computer applications to input patient data into electronic health system

EDUCATION

Florida International University | Sweetwater, Florida | December 2019

B.S. in Recreation & Sport Management: Pre-Recreational Therapy & Adaptive Recreation